<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trust | Hugo Academic CV Theme</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/series/trust/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/series/trust/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Trust</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/sharing.jpg</url>
      <title>Trust</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/series/trust/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title> 🌱 CONTACT US</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Azumi Trust warmly invites you to connect with a story of hope, freedom, and heartfelt service where your contact becomes the first step toward belonging, transformation, and community impact in South-East Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-us--azumi-trust&#34;&gt;Contact Us — Azumi Trust&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Knock, and the door will be opened to you.”&lt;/em&gt; — Jesus Christ (Matthew 7:7)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you reach out, you might begin to feel the warmth of a welcoming community ready to listen, support, and walk alongside you. Whether you want to learn more about our mission, volunteer, donate, or simply share a prayer, your voice and presence matter deeply to us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-reach-us&#34;&gt;How to Reach Us&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phone:&lt;/strong&gt; +44 (0)121 772 9756&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WhatsApp:&lt;/strong&gt; +44 (0)7815 123456 (Chat with us anytime for quick questions or to connect with our team)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to call or message — each connection is a chance to open doors of hope and partnership.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;visit-us&#34;&gt;Visit Us&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Azumi House&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
66 Stratford Road, Sparkbrook,&lt;br&gt;
Birmingham, B11 1SZ, UK&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;opening-hours&#34;&gt;Opening Hours:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monday to Friday: 9:00 AM – 5:00 PM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Closed on weekends and public holidays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Imagine stepping through our doors and feeling the peace and welcome that fills every corner.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;directions&#34;&gt;Directions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By public transport:&lt;/strong&gt; Azumi House is a 10-minute walk from Sparkbrook bus station, with frequent buses running from Birmingham city center.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By car:&lt;/strong&gt; Limited parking is available nearby on Stratford Road.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re here to help you find your way—just ask when you call or message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;your-invitation-to-connect&#34;&gt;Your Invitation to Connect&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You might already sense that making contact is more than a formality—it’s the start of a shared journey toward freedom and new life.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through phone, message, or in person, your reach brings you closer to stories of healing, fellowship, and community growth nurtured through Azumi Trust’s Christian ethos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;inspirational-words-for-the-journey&#34;&gt;Inspirational Words for the Journey&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Ask, and it will be given to you; seek, and you will find; knock, and the door will be opened to you.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
— Jesus Christ (Matthew 7:7)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Faith is taking the first step even when you don’t see the whole staircase.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
— Martin Luther King Jr.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Prayer does not change God, but it changes him who prays.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
— Soren Kierkegaard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you prepare to reach out or step through the door, know that you become part of a caring circle—a community woven with prayers, voices, and hands creating freedom and peace for all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feel&lt;/em&gt; the connection growing &lt;em&gt;hear&lt;/em&gt; the invitation whispering gently—and &lt;em&gt;see&lt;/em&gt; how together, we can build a brighter tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;text-center flex items-center justify-center&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/en/donate&#34;&gt;
&lt;button class=&#34;justify-center items-center rounded-full bg-gradient-to-r from-primary-500 to-primary-600 dark:from-primary-800 dark:to-primary-900 px-8 pt-4 pb-4 sm:px-2 sm:pb-2 text-lg sm:text-base font-semibold text-white shadow-sm hover:bg-primary-500&#34;&gt;
  Donate Now - Transform Lives
&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 🌱 HOW CAN I HELP?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-you-can-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-you-can-help/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Azumi Trust warmly invites you into a journey of hope and transformation where &lt;em&gt;your help, your contribution, and your donation&lt;/em&gt; become the seeds of change that bloom in the lives of individuals and families in need across South-East Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-you-can-help-and-contribute&#34;&gt;How You Can Help and Contribute&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“As you read these words, you might begin to feel the quiet power of your generosity—how with each act of giving, you both uplift others and softly transform yourself.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your support for Azumi Trust can take many heartfelt forms—each one a doorway to healing and belonging:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Praying:&lt;/strong&gt; Feel the strength of community prayer wrapping around those we serve, quietly offering peace and hope in ways words alone cannot express. As you pray, you are joining a spiritual network that supports transformation from the inside out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sharing Information:&lt;/strong&gt; Simply sharing news about Azumi Trust, our projects, or events invites new hearts and hands into this caring circle. Imagine how your small act of telling someone can spark a chain of giving and kindness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volunteering:&lt;/strong&gt; Picture yourself stepping gently into the lives of those we serve—offering time, listening ears, and caring hands. Each moment you give is an opportunity to sow seeds of hope that grow in unexpected and beautiful ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Donating Food:&lt;/strong&gt; Visualize the relief and gratitude as a family receives nourishing meals through your giving. Every item you donate feeds not just bodies but strengthens spirits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Donating Preloved Household Items:&lt;/strong&gt; See the smile of someone settling into a new home, comforted by the thoughtful gifts you provide—each item a tangible sign that they are not forgotten.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Donating Services:&lt;/strong&gt; Whether it’s skilled counseling, tutoring, or practical help, your donated services build bridges to a better tomorrow, restoring dignity and independence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Donating Space or Facilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Envision community projects flourishing in the rooms or grounds you offer—places where healing, connection, and growth take root.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Donating Money:&lt;/strong&gt; Every pound you give plants a seed of freedom, shelter, and renewal. Your financial support fuels vital projects like Azumi House, community gardening, and outreach programs that touch hundreds of lives yearly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-we-do-with-your-donation&#34;&gt;What We Do with Your Donation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Sometimes, you may realize that your generosity today is the best choice you can make—not only transforming lives in our community but gently transforming your own heart as well.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Azumi Trust, your donation blossoms into practical and spiritual support:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Azumi House:&lt;/strong&gt; Providing safe, low-rent housing for disadvantaged Christian men, your gift offers stability and a welcoming home where healing begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Projects:&lt;/strong&gt; From the Hope Garden’s healing spaces, to Ladies’ Day fellowship, to the Children&amp;rsquo;s Club’s joy and learning, your giving nurtures growth and community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interfaith Bridge Building:&lt;/strong&gt; Your support fosters understanding, respect, and peace among diverse faith groups, creating a stronger, more united neighborhood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Ministry &amp;amp; Outreach:&lt;/strong&gt; You empower grassroots ministries and pastoral care, bringing advocacy, resources, and care to those who need it most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;engaging-and-connecting-with-giving&#34;&gt;Engaging and Connecting with Giving&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feel&lt;/em&gt; the warmth spreading through the community because of your kindness. &lt;em&gt;Hear&lt;/em&gt; the soft voices of gratitude echoing through lives you help rebuild. &lt;em&gt;See&lt;/em&gt; the bright future unfolding with every hand extended and every heart encouraged. &lt;em&gt;Know&lt;/em&gt; the deep peace that arises when you become part of something larger—a mission of hope and love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes-to-inspire-your-giving&#34;&gt;Quotes to Inspire Your Giving&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.”&lt;/em&gt; — Mahatma Gandhi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“You can’t separate peace from freedom because no one can be at peace unless he has his freedom.”&lt;/em&gt; — Malcolm X&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Service is the rent we pay for the privilege of living on this earth.”&lt;/em&gt; — Shirley Chisholm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Love cannot remain by itself — it has no meaning. Love has to be put into action and that action is service.”&lt;/em&gt; — Mother Teresa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;your-invitation&#34;&gt;Your Invitation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you choose to contribute—whether through prayer, sharing, volunteering, donating goods, space, services, or funds—you quietly become part of a loving community changing lives and nurturing hope.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Imagine&lt;/em&gt; the joy that blooms in each heart you touch—and feel how, in giving, you too are transformed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To support Azumi Trust is to step into a story of love made real, where your gifts create freedom, peace, and new life for all.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;You might begin to feel how, with a simple choice today, doors of hope quietly open for someone in need. As you explore ways to help, imagine your generosity softly blooming into freedom and new life for families throughout our community. When you decide to contribute, notice the subtle shift—not only in others&amp;rsquo; lives, but within your own heart—as kindness flows outward and gently grows. Picture the relief and warmth your gift brings, and as you consider giving, sense a growing connection and purpose taking root within you. By choosing to support Azumi Trust now, you become part of a caring circle, weaving strength and peace into every life touched—including your own.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;text-center flex items-center justify-center&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/en/donate&#34;&gt;
&lt;button class=&#34;justify-center items-center rounded-full bg-gradient-to-r from-primary-500 to-primary-600 dark:from-primary-800 dark:to-primary-900 px-8 pt-4 pb-4 sm:px-2 sm:pb-2 text-lg sm:text-base font-semibold text-white shadow-sm hover:bg-primary-500&#34;&gt;
  Donate Now - Transform Lives
&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 🌱 WHAT WE DO</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-us--azumi-trust&#34;&gt;About Us — Azumi Trust&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Where the Spirit of the Lord is, there is freedom.”&lt;/em&gt; — 2 Corinthians 3:17&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Picture yourself stepping into a space where &lt;strong&gt;freedom&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;hope&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;community&lt;/strong&gt; bloom in the heart of South-East Birmingham. Here, at Azumi Trust, our name—&lt;em&gt;Azumi&lt;/em&gt;—rings rich with meaning. Rooted in the Persian word for “freedom” or “liberty,” it travels through diverse Middle Eastern and South Asian languages—Luri, Pashto, Kurdish, Hindko, Baluchi, Hindi, Urdu, Punjabi, Bengali, Kashmiri—carrying the promise of liberty to all corners of human experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you sense that gift, imagine how that freedom isn’t just a word here; it is lived in every handshake, every conversation, every moment of care extended across cultures, ages, and faiths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-story-and-mission-following-the-spirit&#34;&gt;Our Story and Mission: Following the Spirit&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founded in &lt;strong&gt;1991&lt;/strong&gt; by Dr. Robin Fisher, a compassionate GP who witnessed deep hardship in Sparkbrook’s drug-affected community, Azumi Trust has grown from a humble outreach into a vibrant Christian charity. Though the original medical practice and drug treatment closed mid-1990s, our vision—&lt;em&gt;to follow where God is working&lt;/em&gt;—endures and expands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might hear echoes of the past as youth clubs once filled Azumi House’s rooms with laughter and learning; see children kicking balls with the Azumi Tigers football team; or feel the gentle warmth of mothers gathering in groups that blossom into friendship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Trust doesn’t seek to create projects on its own; instead, it accompanies passionate community members and seasoned Christian workers who simply want to &lt;em&gt;get on with&lt;/em&gt; serving, unburdened by red tape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;azumi-house--a-home-a-haven&#34;&gt;Azumi House — A Home, A Haven&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;flex justify-center	&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-full&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;Azumi-house.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Azumi House&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step closer to &lt;strong&gt;Azumi House&lt;/strong&gt;, the heart of our operations and a symbol of transformation. Once a family home, then a GP surgery, Azumi House has been a sanctuary since our purchase in &lt;strong&gt;1997&lt;/strong&gt; with support from Christ Church Sparkbrook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine the walls that have housed over two dozen men across more than a dozen nationalities—young, single Christians who find refuge here. Imagine the reflections in the large ground floor rooms that once echoed with youth club chatter, now transformed into welcoming residential spaces, while “The Workshop” remains alive as a place for prayer and intimate community meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This building is more than bricks; it’s a living story, a &lt;em&gt;vehicle&lt;/em&gt; inviting others onboard to journey together in hope, sharing experiences and resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azumi House stands as a cornerstone of Azumi Trust’s mission, embodying a rich history of transformation and community support in South-East Birmingham. Originally a family home turned GP surgery in the 1980s, it became central to the Trust’s work when Dr. Robin Fisher, the founder of Azumi Trust, took over the practice. In 1997, with the help of Christ Church Sparkbrook and a major donor, the Trust purchased the building, marking a new chapter of dedicated service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine Azumi House as more than just a building—it&amp;rsquo;s a sanctuary of hope and healing. Over the years, it has provided a safe, low-rent home primarily for disadvantaged Christian single men, often young, from more than a dozen nationalities. The first floor has long been home to these men, reflecting the Trust’s commitment to creating a community where residents are supported pastorally and encouraged to grow in faith and independence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ground floor has witnessed decades of vibrant community activity. It once housed a youth club and homework club aimed at local children and young people, mainly run by members of Christ Church but open to all in the neighborhood. It has been a base for various projects like the ‘Bright Sparks’ mother and toddler group and even the ‘Azumi Tigers’ football team. The Trust’s ethos has always been to “follow what God is doing,” supporting existing passionate community efforts rather than setting up new structures unnecessarily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2008, the Trust renovated an annex known as ‘The Workshop,’ providing an additional meeting space with separate access and facilities. This room continues today as a prayer room and a place for small community gatherings. Although the two large ground floor rooms were eventually converted for residential use following the opening of the new Christ Church building nearby in 2012, the Workshop remains a beacon of outreach and spiritual support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azumi House also offers guest accommodations upstairs, welcoming visitors of residents and short-term guests, reinforcing the sense of community and hospitality at the heart of the Trust’s vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you imagine the walls of Azumi House, envision a place alive with stories of restoration—a place where freedom, peace, and new life blossom in alignment with the Trust’s strapline from 2 Corinthians 3:17: &lt;em&gt;“Where the Spirit of the Lord is, there is freedom.”&lt;/em&gt; The building acts as both a physical and spiritual ‘vehicle,’ enabling various groups and individuals to journey together, share resources, and deepen their impact in South-East Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This living space continues to evolve, with a renewed focus on building a mutually supportive Christian community while serving and welcoming the broader local area. Azumi House remains a tangible expression of Azumi Trust’s mission—offering shelter, support, and a faithful presence amid one of the UK’s most diverse and dynamic urban neighborhoods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you picture yourself walking through its doors, you’d encounter not only a safe home but a community where hope flourishes, friendships are formed, and lives are quietly transformed by genuine care and compassion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hope-therapeutic-garden--growing-healing-together&#34;&gt;Hope Therapeutic Garden — Growing Healing Together&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;flex justify-center	&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-full&#34; &gt;
          &lt;img alt=&#34;Hope Therapeutic Garden&#34; 
               srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/heaven-garden_hu_7558a938d7387f46.webp 320w, http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/heaven-garden_hu_2f9aaf033c3f5baf.webp 480w, http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/heaven-garden_hu_c2ad12fe6031c0cb.webp 512w&#34;
               sizes=&#34;(max-width: 480px) 100vw, (max-width: 768px) 90vw, (max-width: 1024px) 80vw, 760px&#34;
               src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/heaven-garden_hu_7558a938d7387f46.webp&#34;
               width=&#34;512&#34;
               height=&#34;512&#34;
               loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now imagine the gentle hands tending rows of vegetables, the soft rustle of leaves in a garden born out of compassion. The &lt;strong&gt;Hope Therapeutic Garden&lt;/strong&gt;, started in &lt;strong&gt;2008&lt;/strong&gt;, offers more than green growth—it nurtures healing, friendship, and belonging for those marginalized by ethnicity, disability, or status.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visualize people arriving with anticipation, perhaps singing joyous songs like &lt;em&gt;“I’m on Top Of The World”&lt;/em&gt;, stepping off their buses, ready to embrace the peace found in soil and fellowship. Feel the comforting aroma of earth mingling with warm cups of tea shared beneath open skies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over twelve years, retreats into the Cotswolds or camping trips challenged by British weather have woven stories of resilience and joy. Annual BBQs and celebrations mark community milestones, birthdays, and global traditions—each event strengthening bonds and echoing the love of Christ in action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants learn new skills—composting, grafting, growing exotic crops—and form friendships that become lifelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope Therapeutic Garden, also lovingly known as Hope Garden, is a verdant sanctuary of healing, fellowship, and renewal deeply rooted in the heart of South-East Birmingham. Born in 2008 from a compassionate vision sparked by Mary Carroll, who after witnessing the struggles of destitute asylum seekers living nearby, sought to create a place where marginalized individuals—especially women suffering from social exclusion, poor mental health, and other challenges—could find rest, support, and community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine a wild, uncared-for garden transformed by gentle hands into an inviting space where people of many backgrounds gather over tea and conversation, healing through connection and the nurturing power of nature. Mary saw growing and harvesting not only as practical acts but as profound healing practices—moments where people relax, share stories, and experience Christ’s love in action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The garden became a refuge from harsh realities—where participants could thrive emotionally, mentally, and socially. The early attendees were residents of nearby Hope House and visitors from health drop-in sessions at Azumi House. For many, the garden offered better nourishment than medicine—both physical from the fresh produce grown and mental from the community’s support. One participant even celebrated arriving at Hope Garden by singing “I’m on Top of the World,” a joyful expression of the freedom and happiness the garden inspired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope Garden also nurtured growth beyond plants: retreats to serene locations like the Cotswolds, Belmont Abbey, and British parks enriched participants’ spirits. Annual gatherings, like summer BBQs and celebrations of cultural days such as World Africa Day, Easter egg hunts, and Christmas festivities, knit diverse individuals into a warm, extended family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volunteers play a vital role here—faithful people like Nathalie, Mauricio, and Pauline who go the extra mile, whether by driving participants to events, delivering food, offering advice, or simply being dependable friends. Despite challenges like funding shortages or unexpected hurdles (heating failures, last-minute meal preparations), the faith and dedication of this small but mighty team keep the garden flourishing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through Hope Garden, people learn valuable skills such as composting, grafting, and vegetable cultivation. The project also forged connections with organizations like Ryton Organic Gardens through initiatives like “Growing From Your Roots,” which celebrate heritage, gardening traditions, and cultural exchange.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you envision Hope Therapeutic Garden, feel the gentle rustle of leaves and the quiet hum of friendship growing alongside vegetables. Hear laughter blending with bird song. See faces brightened by shared meals and nature’s beauty. Know that here, in this vibrant patch of earth, freedom, peace, and new life take root—offering hope not just as a word, but as a lived reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope Garden stands as a testament to Azumi Trust’s spirit: to &lt;em&gt;follow where God is working&lt;/em&gt;, to foster belonging among the marginalized, and to share love that transforms both the soil and the soul. It invites all who enter to be part of a growing story—one of nurture, healing, and joyful life renewed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;volunteers-and-trustees--the-heartbeat-of-our-work&#34;&gt;Volunteers and Trustees — The Heartbeat of Our Work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Behind every garden bloom and every sunset over Azumi House stand &lt;strong&gt;volunteers&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;trustees&lt;/strong&gt;. Picture Nathalie and Mauricio, Columban missionaries pressing beyond their comfort zones to serve, or Pauline driving the minibus, delivering life-saving support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel the warmth radiating from their honest dedication—the countless acts of kindness like delivering meals, guiding those lost through paperwork, and holding hands during hard times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our trustees, Liz, Mike, and Eve, quietly navigate challenges—conflict resolution, sourcing resources, stewarding finances—ensuring the Trust’s foundation remains strong and welcoming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;buildings-and-infrastructure--foundations-for-growth&#34;&gt;Buildings and Infrastructure — Foundations for Growth&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visualize Azumi House standing firm on Stratford Road, its rooms buzzing with purpose—community meetings, prayer groups, welcoming visitors in guest rooms, educational activities, and spaces for healing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine small gardens growing next door, extending the Reach of Hope Therapeutic Garden, and the promise of new community centers on the horizon designed for fellowship and outreach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;looking-ahead--growing-the-circle-of-impact&#34;&gt;Looking Ahead — Growing the Circle of Impact&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you imagine the thriving future of Azumi Trust, sense the gentle momentum of new partnerships and projects—extending our embrace to even more who need freedom, peace, and renewal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future plans include expanding garden spaces, offering more supported accommodation, deepening interfaith dialogue, and partnering with grassroots projects who share our Christian ethos but seek a stable structure to amplify their mission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each initiative, every new smile formed in the light of faith and care, is a testimony that the Spirit’s work here is alive and growing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;join-us--become-part-of-this-living-story&#34;&gt;Join Us — Become Part of This Living Story&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now, you might feel a quiet stirring—a gentle nudge inviting you to step closer and belong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are warmly invited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pray with us, weaving spiritual strength&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Volunteer your time, skills, or care&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share our story, spreading hope&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Donate resources, money, or space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As you do, you may notice how your kindness flows outward, planting seeds not just in others&amp;rsquo; lives, but also flowering within your own heart.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;experience-azumi-trust-through-your-senses&#34;&gt;Experience Azumi Trust Through Your Senses&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feel&lt;/em&gt; the gentle warmth of community weaving through local streets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hear&lt;/em&gt; laughter rising over freshly turned soil and shared meals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;See&lt;/em&gt; lives renewed where hardship once overshadowed hope&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Know&lt;/em&gt; the deep peace found in freedom and belonging—freedom that Azumi so beautifully names and embodies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.”&lt;/em&gt; — Mahatma Gandhi&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;“Where the Spirit of the Lord is, there is freedom.”&lt;/em&gt; — 2 Corinthians 3:17&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;“Love cannot remain by itself — it has no meaning. Love has to be put into action and that action is service.”&lt;/em&gt; — Mother Teresa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azumi Trust is not just a charity—it is a &lt;em&gt;movement&lt;/em&gt; of freedom, faith, and fellowship, quietly changing lives in South-East Birmingham and inviting you to join the journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Imagine&lt;/em&gt; your story intertwining here—and feel how giving, serving, and belonging bring freedom not only to others but within yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-purpose-of-azumi-trust&#34;&gt;The Purpose of Azumi Trust&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azumi Trust stands as a beacon of hope and transformation in South-East Birmingham, deeply rooted in a Christian mission to bring freedom, peace, and new life to marginalized individuals and families. For over three decades, this charitable organization has tirelessly worked to nurture a community where love is not just felt but lived, reflecting the profound truth that *“Love cannot remain by itself — it has no meaning. Love has to be put into action and that action is service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At its heart, Azumi Trust exists to serve those often overlooked—people affected by age, ethnicity, disability, poverty, or displacement—offering not only practical assistance but a compassionate, faith-filled community. Inspired by the life and teachings of Christ, the Trust’s purpose is far-reaching yet deeply personal: to foster belonging, well-being, and spiritual growth in neighborhoods where these gifts are most needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Mahatma Gandhi wisely said, &lt;em&gt;“The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.”&lt;/em&gt; Azumi Trust exemplifies this by placing service at the center of its work, creating spaces where lives can be rebuilt, relationships restored, and hope renewed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;main-activities-of-azumi-trust&#34;&gt;Main Activities of Azumi Trust&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;azumi-house-a-safe-haven&#34;&gt;Azumi House: A Safe Haven&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the Trust’s flagship initiatives is &lt;strong&gt;Azumi House&lt;/strong&gt;, providing secure, low-rent accommodation for disadvantaged Christian single men, particularly in the Sparkbrook area. This project offers more than shelter—it is a place of refuge, pastoral care, and community engagement, enabling residents to regain stability and actively participate in local church life and ministry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;active-community-projects&#34;&gt;Active Community Projects&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azumi Trust supports three vibrant community projects that directly benefit local families and individuals:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hope Garden Project:&lt;/strong&gt; A sanctuary for asylum seekers and refugees where healing flourishes through gardening skills, fellowship, and mutual support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ladies’ Day:&lt;/strong&gt; Weekly gatherings that nurture fellowship and encouragement among local women, strengthening bonds of sisterhood.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Children’s Club:&lt;/strong&gt; Providing a safe, joyful space for children to learn, play, and grow in a supportive environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, these projects embody the belief that &lt;em&gt;“Small acts, when multiplied by millions of people, can transform the world.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;interfaith-bridge-building&#34;&gt;Interfaith Bridge Building&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Living their Christian faith with humility and openness, Azumi Trust fosters respectful dialogue and cooperation among people of different faiths. By sharing Christ’s love with sensitivity to diversity, the Trust creates opportunities for deeper community connection and mutual growth—inviting all to experience the &lt;em&gt;well-being&lt;/em&gt; that comes from peace and understanding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;collaborative-ministry-and-outreach&#34;&gt;Collaborative Ministry and Outreach&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azumi Trust also acts as an umbrella organization, partnering with like-minded Christian groups to provide governance, financial support, and facilities, ensuring that grassroots projects can thrive without bureaucratic burdens. Their outreach and pastoral care programs impact hundreds of lives annually—offering advocacy, support, and new opportunities for those in need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-spirit-of-freedom-peace-and-hope&#34;&gt;A Spirit of Freedom, Peace, and Hope&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Trust’s name, &lt;em&gt;Azumi&lt;/em&gt;, means freedom—an ethos reflected in every facet of their work. As Malcolm X observed, &lt;em&gt;“You can’t separate peace from freedom because no one can be at peace unless he has his freedom.”&lt;/em&gt; Through compassionate service, Azumi Trust helps individuals reclaim this freedom, fostering peace not only in external circumstances but within hearts and communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;closing-reflection&#34;&gt;Closing Reflection&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azumi Trust’s mission reminds us that &lt;em&gt;“The greatness of a community is most accurately measured by the compassionate actions of its members.”&lt;/em&gt; Their unwavering commitment to serving Birmingham’s diverse communities, one life at a time, eloquently illustrates how faith in action multiplies hope beyond measure—changing lives and transforming selves alike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To support or learn more about Azumi Trust’s inspiring work is to step into a story of love, freedom, and flourishing community.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;text-center flex items-center justify-center&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/en/donate&#34;&gt;
&lt;button class=&#34;justify-center items-center rounded-full bg-gradient-to-r from-primary-500 to-primary-600 dark:from-primary-800 dark:to-primary-900 px-8 pt-4 pb-4 sm:px-2 sm:pb-2 text-lg sm:text-base font-semibold text-white shadow-sm hover:bg-primary-500&#34;&gt;
  Donate Now - Transform Lives
&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🌱 DONATE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/donate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;donate--supporting-the-vision&#34;&gt;Donate — Supporting the Vision&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Honest hearts produce honest actions.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Azumi Trust is a Company Limited by Guarantee. Registered in England and Wales. Company Number: 07247132 Registered Charity Number: 1138663&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you take a moment here, you might begin to notice how honest generosity quietly shapes lives because every gift, offered with sincerity, becomes a true act of hope. We honestly say a &lt;strong&gt;big thank you&lt;/strong&gt; to every individual, church, and organisation who has already given—without your dedicated support, we simply would not be able to impact lives the way we do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our work is real, and so are the needs—bus fares for volunteers, gardening tools, and trusted spaces for those who feel alone. It&amp;rsquo;s &lt;strong&gt;your honest support&lt;/strong&gt; that helps us reach people like &lt;em&gt;Kevin&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Sarah&lt;/em&gt;, offering new beginnings where they are needed most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are warmly invited now to become a part of what we do, just as you are. &lt;em&gt;And as you decide to give, you may quietly notice a sense of connection and honest purpose growing within you—knowing that your gift truly matters.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ways-you-can-give&#34;&gt;Ways You Can Give&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-donate-online&#34;&gt;1. Donate Online&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can give, securely and honestly, right here:&lt;br&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to support our mortgage fund directly, visit:&lt;br&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gift Aid:&lt;/strong&gt; If you&amp;rsquo;re a UK taxpayer, please consider selecting Gift Aid when giving online—it allows us to reclaim tax already paid, at &lt;em&gt;no extra cost to you&lt;/em&gt;. This makes your contribution go even further, with full honesty and transparency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note:&lt;/em&gt; 3% of each online gift is given to Stewardship, a UK Christian charity, ensuring every penny is used honestly for the good of communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-bank-transfer&#34;&gt;2. Bank Transfer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may choose to set up a standing order or one-off payment:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sort Code: &lt;strong&gt;30 96 28&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Account Number: &lt;strong&gt;17913960&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IBAN: &lt;strong&gt;GB18LOYD30962817913960&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BIC: &lt;strong&gt;LOYDGB21274&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you wish to help a specific project, let us know by note, email, or simply specify it on your donation—so your honest intention is fully reflected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-cheque&#34;&gt;3. Cheque&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make cheques payable to &lt;strong&gt;‘Azumi Trust’&lt;/strong&gt; and post to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azumi Trust&lt;br&gt;
56 Grantham Road&lt;br&gt;
Birmingham, B11 1LX, England, UK&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;your-gift-in-action&#34;&gt;Your Gift in Action&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Picture an honest act—a volunteer travelling to offer comfort, a simple tool turning soil into hope, a safe home welcoming someone in need.&lt;/em&gt; Each moment is made possible by your sincere generosity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you choose to give, notice the gentle assurance that comes from being part of a community built honestly on love, trust, and meaningful change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Knock, and the door will be opened to you.”&lt;/em&gt; — Matthew 7:7&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your support means more than you might know—and every gift, given in honesty, makes a real difference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
