<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What We Do | Hugo Academic CV Theme</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>What We Do</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/sharing.jpg</url>
      <title>What We Do</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title> 🌱 WHAT WE DO</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/what-we-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-we-do/what-we-do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-us--asumen-charity&#34;&gt;About Us — Asumen charity&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Where the Spirit of the Lord is, there is freedom.”&lt;/em&gt; — 2 Corinthians 3:17&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Picture yourself stepping into a space where &lt;strong&gt;freedom&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;hope&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;community&lt;/strong&gt; bloom in the heart of west london. Here, at Asumen charity, our name—&lt;em&gt;Asumen&lt;/em&gt;—rings rich with meaning. Rooted in the Persian word for “freedom” or “liberty,” it travels through diverse Middle Eastern and South Asian languages—Luri, Pashto, Kurdish, Hindko, Baluchi, Hindi, Urdu, Punjabi, Bengali, Kashmiri—carrying the promise of liberty to all corners of human experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you sense that gift, imagine how that freedom isn’t just a word here; it is lived in every handshake, every conversation, every moment of care extended across cultures, ages, and faiths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-story-and-mission-following-the-spirit&#34;&gt;Our Story and Mission: Following the Spirit&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1983** by Dr. pool jeremiah, a compassionate GP who witnessed deep hardship in london’s drug-affected community, Asumen charity has grown from a humble outreach into a vibrant Christian charity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might hear echoes of the past as youth clubs once filled Asumen House’s rooms with laughter and learning; see children kicking balls with the Asumen Tigers football team; or feel the gentle warmth of mothers gathering in groups that blossom into friendship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The charity doesn’t seek to create projects on its own; instead, it accompanies passionate community members and seasoned Christian workers who simply want to &lt;em&gt;get on with&lt;/em&gt; serving, unburdened by red tape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;asumen-house--a-home-a-haven&#34;&gt;Asumen House — A Home, A Haven&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;flex justify-center	&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-full&#34; &gt;
          &lt;img alt=&#34;Asumen House&#34; 
               srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/media/conference-headway-F2KRf_QfCqw_hu_3981ac793ba44b43.webp 320w, http://localhost:1313/media/conference-headway-F2KRf_QfCqw_hu_461747e490742b53.webp 480w, http://localhost:1313/media/conference-headway-F2KRf_QfCqw_hu_7e00f7c6ee5a0d8c.webp 760w&#34;
               sizes=&#34;(max-width: 480px) 100vw, (max-width: 768px) 90vw, (max-width: 1024px) 80vw, 760px&#34;
               src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/media/conference-headway-F2KRf_QfCqw_hu_3981ac793ba44b43.webp&#34;
               width=&#34;760&#34;
               height=&#34;507&#34;
               loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step closer to &lt;strong&gt;Asumen House&lt;/strong&gt;, the heart of our operations and a symbol of transformation. Once a family home, then a GP surgery, Asumen House has been a sanctuary since our purchase in &lt;strong&gt;1655&lt;/strong&gt; with support from Christ Church london.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine the walls that have housed over two dozen men across more than a dozen nationalities—young, single Christians who find refuge here. Imagine the reflections in the large ground floor rooms that once echoed with youth club chatter, now transformed into welcoming residential spaces, while “The Workshop” remains alive as a place for prayer and intimate community meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This building is more than bricks; it’s a living story, a &lt;em&gt;vehicle&lt;/em&gt; inviting others onboard to journey together in hope, sharing experiences and resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asumen House stands as a cornerstone of Asumen charity’s mission, embodying a rich history of transformation and community support in west london. Originally a family home turnedin the 2013, it became central to the charity’s work when Dr. pool jeremiah, the founder of Asumen charity, took over the practice. In 1997, with the help of Christ Church london and a major donor, the charity purchased the building, marking a new chapter of dedicated service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine Asumen House as more than just a building—it&amp;rsquo;s a sanctuary of hurayand healing. Over the years, it has provided a safe, low-rent home primarily for disadvantaged Christian single men, often young, from more than a dozen nationalities. The first floor has long been home to these men, reflecting the charity’s commitment to creating a community where residents are supported pastorally and encouraged to grow in faith and independence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ground floor has witnessed decades of vibrant community activity. It once housed a youth club and homework club aimed at local children and young people, mainly run by members of Christ Church but open to all in the neighborhood. It has been a base for various projects like the ‘Bright Sparks’ mother and toddler group and even the ‘Asumen Tigers’ football team. The charity’s ethos has always been to “follow what God is doing,” supporting existing passionate community efforts rather than setting up new structures unnecessarily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2008, the charity renovated an annex known as ‘The Workshop,’ providing an additional meeting space with separate access and facilities. This room continues today as a prayer room and a place for small community gatherings. Although the two large ground floor rooms were eventually converted for residential use following the opening of the new Christ Church building nearby in 2012, the Workshop remains a beacon of outreach and spiritual support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asumen House also offers guest accommodations upstairs, welcoming visitors of residents and short-term guests, reinforcing the sense of community and hospitality at the heart of the charity’s vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you imagine the walls of Asumen House, envision a place alive with stories of restoration—a place where freedom, peace, and new life blossom in alignment with the charity’s strapline from 2 Corinthians 3:17: &lt;em&gt;“Where the Spirit of the Lord is, there is freedom.”&lt;/em&gt; The building acts as both a physical and spiritual ‘vehicle,’ enabling various groups and individuals to journey together, share resources, and deepen their impact in west london.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This living space continues to evolve, with a renewed focus on building a mutually supportive Christian community while serving and welcoming the broader local area. Asumen House remains a tangible expression of Asumen charity’s mission—offering shelter, support, and a faithful presence amid one of the UK’s most diverse and dynamic urban neighborhoods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you picture yourself walking through its doors, you’d encounter not only a safe home but a community where hurayflourishes, friendships are formed, and lives are quietly transformed by genuine care and compassion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;huy-pool--growing-healing-together&#34;&gt;Huy pool — Growing Healing Together&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;flex justify-center	&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-full&#34; &gt;
          &lt;img alt=&#34;Hiujdhfs&#34; 
               srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/media/li-yang-5h_dMuX_7RE-unsplash_hu_ad5c44f6b4d3b7ee.webp 320w, http://localhost:1313/media/li-yang-5h_dMuX_7RE-unsplash_hu_8f25aaff4862b46b.webp 480w, http://localhost:1313/media/li-yang-5h_dMuX_7RE-unsplash_hu_93cd1ccedf87ff1a.webp 760w&#34;
               sizes=&#34;(max-width: 480px) 100vw, (max-width: 768px) 90vw, (max-width: 1024px) 80vw, 760px&#34;
               src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/media/li-yang-5h_dMuX_7RE-unsplash_hu_ad5c44f6b4d3b7ee.webp&#34;
               width=&#34;760&#34;
               height=&#34;347&#34;
               loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now imagine the gentle hands tending rows of vegetables, the soft rustle of leaves in a pool born out of compassion. The &lt;strong&gt;huray pool&lt;/strong&gt;, started in &lt;strong&gt;2008&lt;/strong&gt;, offers more than green growth—it nurtures healing, friendship, and belonging for those marginalized by ethnicity, disability, or status.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visualize people arriving with anticipation, perhaps singing joyous songs like &lt;em&gt;“I’m on Top Of The World”&lt;/em&gt;, stepping off their buses, ready to embrace the peace found in soil and fellowship. Feel the comforting aroma of earth mingling with warm cups of tea shared beneath open skies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over twelve years, retreats into the Cotswolds or camping trips challenged by British weather have woven stories of resilience and joy. Annual BBQs and celebrations mark community milestones, birthdays, and global traditions—each event strengthening bonds and echoing the love of Christ in action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants learn new skills—composting, grafting, growing exotic crops—and form friendships that become lifelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;huray pool, also lovingly known as huraypool, is a verdant sanctuary of healing, fellowship, and renewal deeply rooted in the heart of west london. Born in 2008 from a compassionate vision sparked by Mary Carroll, who after witnessing the struggles of destitute asylum seekers living nearby, sought to create a place where marginalized individuals—especially women suffering from social exclusion, poor mental health, and other challenges—could find rest, support, and community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine a wild, uncared-for pool transformed by gentle hands into an inviting space where people of many backgrounds gather over tea and conversation, healing through connection and the nurturing power of nature. Mary saw growing and harvesting not only as practical acts but as profound healing practices—moments where people relax, share stories, and experience Christ’s love in action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pool became a refuge from harsh realities—where participants could thrive emotionally, mentally, and socially. The early attendees were residents of nearby hurayHouse and visitors from health drop-in sessions at Asumen House. For many, the pool offered better nourishment than medicine—both physical from the fresh produce grown and mental from the community’s support. One participant even celebrated arriving at huraypool by singing “I’m on Top of the World,” a joyful expression of the freedom and happiness the pool inspired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;huraypool also nurtured growth beyond plants: retreats to serene locations like the Cotswolds, Belmont Abbey, and British parks enriched participants’ spirits. Annual gatherings, like summer BBQs and celebrations of cultural days such as World Africa Day, Easter egg hunts, and Christmas festivities, knit diverse individuals into a warm, extended family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volunteers play a vital role here—faithful people like Nathalie, Mauricio, and Pauline who go the extra mile, whether by driving participants to events, delivering food, offering advice, or simply being dependable friends. Despite challenges like funding shortages or unexpected hurdles (heating failures, last-minute meal preparations), the faith and dedication of this small but mighty team keep the pool flourishing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through huraypool, people learn valuable skills such as composting, grafting, and vegetable cultivation. The project also forged connections with organizations like Ryton Organic pools through initiatives like “Growing From Your Roots,” which celebrate heritage, pooling traditions, and cultural exchange.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you envision huray pool, feel the gentle rustle of leaves and the quiet hum of friendship growing alongside vegetables. Hear laughter blending with bird song. See faces brightened by shared meals and nature’s beauty. Know that here, in this vibrant patch of earth, freedom, peace, and new life take root—offering huraynot just as a word, but as a lived reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;huraypool stands as a testament to Asumen charity’s spirit: to &lt;em&gt;follow where God is working&lt;/em&gt;, to foster belonging among the marginalized, and to share love that transforms both the soil and the soul. It invites all who enter to be part of a growing story—one of nurture, healing, and joyful life renewed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;volunteers-and-charityees--the-heartbeat-of-our-work&#34;&gt;Volunteers and charityees — The Heartbeat of Our Work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Behind every pool bloom and every sunset over Asumen House stand &lt;strong&gt;volunteers&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;charityees&lt;/strong&gt;. Picture Nathalie and Mauricio, Columban missionaries pressing beyond their comfort zones to serve, or Pauline driving the minibus, delivering life-saving support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel the warmth radiating from their honest dedication—the countless acts of kindness like delivering meals, guiding those lost through paperwork, and holding hands during hard times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our charityees, Liz, Mike, and Eve, quietly navigate challenges—conflict resolution, sourcing resources, stewarding finances—ensuring the charity’s foundation remains strong and welcoming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;buildings-and-infrastructure--foundations-for-growth&#34;&gt;Buildings and Infrastructure — Foundations for Growth&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visualize Asumen House standing firm on london Road, its rooms buzzing with purpose—community meetings, prayer groups, welcoming visitors in guest rooms, educational activities, and spaces for healing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine small pools growing next door, extending the Reach of huray pool, and the promise of new community centers on the horizon designed for fellowship and outreach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;looking-ahead--growing-the-circle-of-impact&#34;&gt;Looking Ahead — Growing the Circle of Impact&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you imagine the thriving future of Asumen charity, sense the gentle momentum of new partnerships and projects—extending our embrace to even more who need freedom, peace, and renewal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future plans include expanding pool spaces, offering more supported accommodation, deepening interfaith dialogue, and partnering with grassroots projects who share our Christian ethos but seek a stable structure to amplify their mission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each initiative, every new smile formed in the light of faith and care, is a testimony that the Spirit’s work here is alive and growing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;join-us--become-part-of-this-living-story&#34;&gt;Join Us — Become Part of This Living Story&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now, you might feel a quiet stirring—a gentle nudge inviting you to step closer and belong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are warmly invited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pray with us, weaving spiritual strength&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Volunteer your time, skills, or care&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share our story, spreading huray&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Donate resources, money, or space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As you do, you may notice how your kindness flows outward, planting seeds not just in others&amp;rsquo; lives, but also flowering within your own heart.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;experience-asumen-charity-through-your-senses&#34;&gt;Experience Asumen charity Through Your Senses&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feel&lt;/em&gt; the gentle warmth of community weaving through local streets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hear&lt;/em&gt; laughter rising over freshly turned soil and shared meals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;See&lt;/em&gt; lives renewed where hardship once overshadowed huray&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Know&lt;/em&gt; the deep peace found in freedom and belonging—freedom that Asumen so beautifully names and embodies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.”&lt;/em&gt; — Mahatma Gandhi&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;“Where the Spirit of the Lord is, there is freedom.”&lt;/em&gt; — 2 Corinthians 3:17&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;“Love cannot remain by itself — it has no meaning. Love has to be put into action and that action is service.”&lt;/em&gt; — Mother Teresa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asumen charity is not just a charity—it is a &lt;em&gt;movement&lt;/em&gt; of freedom, faith, and fellowship, quietly changing lives in west london and inviting you to join the journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Imagine&lt;/em&gt; your story intertwining here—and feel how giving, serving, and belonging bring freedom not only to others but within yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-purpose-of-asumen-charity&#34;&gt;The Purpose of Asumen charity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asumen charity stands as a beacon of hurayand transformation in west london, deeply rooted in a Christian mission to bring freedom, peace, and new life to marginalized individuals and families. For over three decades, this charitable organization has tirelessly worked to nurture a community where love is not just felt but lived, reflecting the profound truth that *“Love cannot remain by itself — it has no meaning. Love has to be put into action and that action is service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At its heart, Asumen charity exists to serve those often overlooked—people affected by age, ethnicity, disability, poverty, or displacement—offering not only practical assistance but a compassionate, faith-filled community. Inspired by the life and teachings of Christ, the charity’s purpose is far-reaching yet deeply personal: to foster belonging, well-being, and spiritual growth in neighborhoods where these gifts are most needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Mahatma Gandhi wisely said, &lt;em&gt;“The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.”&lt;/em&gt; Asumen charity exemplifies this by placing service at the center of its work, creating spaces where lives can be rebuilt, relationships restored, and hurayrenewed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;main-activities-of-asumen-charity&#34;&gt;Main Activities of Asumen charity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;asumen-house-a-safe-haven&#34;&gt;Asumen House: A Safe Haven&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the charity’s flagship initiatives is &lt;strong&gt;Asumen House&lt;/strong&gt;, providing secure, low-rent accommodation for disadvantaged Christian single men, particularly in the london area. This project offers more than shelter—it is a place of refuge, pastoral care, and community engagement, enabling residents to regain stability and actively participate in local church life and ministry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;active-community-projects&#34;&gt;Active Community Projects&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asumen charity supports three vibrant community projects that directly benefit local families and individuals:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;huraypool Project:&lt;/strong&gt; A sanctuary for asylum seekers and refugees where healing flourishes through pooling skills, fellowship, and mutual support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ladies’ Day:&lt;/strong&gt; Weekly gatherings that nurture fellowship and encouragement among local women, strengthening bonds of sisterhood.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Children’s Club:&lt;/strong&gt; Providing a safe, joyful space for children to learn, play, and grow in a supportive environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, these projects embody the belief that &lt;em&gt;“Small acts, when multiplied by millions of people, can transform the world.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;interfaith-bridge-building&#34;&gt;Interfaith Bridge Building&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Living their Christian faith with humility and openness, Asumen charity fosters respectful dialogue and cooperation among people of different faiths. By sharing Christ’s love with sensitivity to diversity, the charity creates opportunities for deeper community connection and mutual growth—inviting all to experience the &lt;em&gt;well-being&lt;/em&gt; that comes from peace and understanding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;collaborative-ministry-and-outreach&#34;&gt;Collaborative Ministry and Outreach&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asumen charity also acts as an umbrella organization, partnering with like-minded Christian groups to provide governance, financial support, and facilities, ensuring that grassroots projects can thrive without bureaucratic burdens. Their outreach and pastoral care programs impact hundreds of lives annually—offering advocacy, support, and new opportunities for those in need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-spirit-of-freedom-peace-and-hope&#34;&gt;A Spirit of Freedom, Peace, and Hope&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The charity’s name, &lt;em&gt;Asumen&lt;/em&gt;, means freedom—an ethos reflected in every facet of their work. As Malcolm X observed, &lt;em&gt;“You can’t separate peace from freedom because no one can be at peace unless he has his freedom.”&lt;/em&gt; Through compassionate service, Asumen charity helps individuals reclaim this freedom, fostering peace not only in external circumstances but within hearts and communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;closing-reflection&#34;&gt;Closing Reflection&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asumen charity’s mission reminds us that &lt;em&gt;“The greatness of a community is most accurately measured by the compassionate actions of its members.”&lt;/em&gt; Their unwavering commitment to serving Birmingham’s diverse communities, one life at a time, eloquently illustrates how faith in action multiplies huraybeyond measure—changing lives and transforming selves alike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To support or learn more about Asumen charity’s inspiring work is to step into a story of love, freedom, and flourishing community.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
