<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terms | Hugo Academic CV Theme</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/series/terms/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/series/terms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Terms</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/sharing.jpg</url>
      <title>Terms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/series/terms/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>⚖️ Terms of Service</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/terms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome-to-connection&#34;&gt;Welcome to Connection!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of Connection&amp;rsquo;s Website, located at 
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use Connection if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: &amp;ldquo;Client&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Your&amp;rdquo; refers to you, the person log on this website and compliant to the Company&amp;rsquo;s terms and conditions. &amp;ldquo;The Company&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Ourselves&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Our&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Us&amp;rdquo;, refers to our Company. &amp;ldquo;Party&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Parties&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;Us&amp;rdquo;, refers to both the Client and ourselves. All terms refer to the offer, acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner for the express purpose of meeting the Client&amp;rsquo;s needs in respect of provision of the Company&amp;rsquo;s stated services, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing law of Great Britain. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalization and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;license&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;License&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unless otherwise stated, Connection and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on Connection. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this from Connection for your own personal use subjected to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;cc-by-nc-nd-40-deed--attribution-noncommercial-noderivs-40-international--creative-commons&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC-ND 4.0 Deed | Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 4.0 International | Creative Commons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;excerpt&#34;&gt;Excerpt&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You do not have to comply with the license for elements of the material in the public domain or where your use is permitted by an applicable exception or limitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-are-free-to&#34;&gt;You are free to:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Share&lt;/strong&gt; — copy and redistribute the material in any medium or format&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The licensor cannot revoke these freedoms as long as you follow the license terms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;under-the-following-terms&#34;&gt;Under the following terms:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attribution&lt;/strong&gt; — You must give 
 , provide a link to the license, and 
 . You may do so in any reasonable manner, but not in any way that suggests the licensor endorses you or your use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NonCommercial&lt;/strong&gt; — You may not use the material for 
 .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NoDerivatives&lt;/strong&gt; — If you 
 the material, you may not distribute the modified material.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No additional restrictions&lt;/strong&gt; — You may not apply legal terms or 
 that legally restrict others from doing anything the license permits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;notices&#34;&gt;Notices:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You do not have to comply with the license for elements of the material in the public domain or where your use is permitted by an applicable 
 .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No warranties are given. The license may not give you all of the permissions necessary for your intended use. For example, other rights such as 
 may limit how you use the material.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hyperlinking-to-our-content&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hyperlinking to our Content&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following organizations may link to our Website without prior written approval:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Government agencies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search engines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;News organizations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online directory distributors may link to our Website in the same manner as they hyperlink to the Websites of other listed businesses; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;System wide Accredited Businesses except soliciting non-profit organizations, charity shopping malls, and charity fundraising groups which may not hyperlink to our Web site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Website information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products and/or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party&amp;rsquo;s site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may consider and approve other link requests from the following types of organizations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;commonly-known consumer and/or business information sources;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dot.com community sites;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;associations or other groups representing charities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;online directory distributors;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;internet portals;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;accounting, law and consulting firms; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;educational institutions and trade associations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will approve link requests from these organizations if we decide that: (a) the link would not make us look unfavorably to ourselves or to our accredited businesses; (b) the organization does not have any negative records with us; (c) the benefit to us from the visibility of the hyperlink compensates the absence of Connection; and (d) the link is in the context of general resource information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These organizations may link to our home page so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party&amp;rsquo;s site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are one of the organizations listed in paragraph 2 above and are interested in linking to our website, you must inform us by sending an e-mail to Connection. Please include your name, your organization name, contact information as well as the URL of your site, a list of any URLs from which you intend to link to our Website, and a list of the URLs on our site to which you would like to link. Wait 2-3 weeks for a response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approved organizations may hyperlink to our Website as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By use of our corporate name; or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By use of the uniform resource locator being linked to; or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By use of any other description of our Website being linked to that makes sense within the context and format of content on the linking party&amp;rsquo;s site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No use of Connection&amp;rsquo;s logo or other artwork will be allowed for linking absent a trademark license agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;iframes&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;iFrames&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without prior approval and written permission, you may not create frames around our Webpages that alter in any way the visual presentation or appearance of our Website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-liability&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content Liability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We shall not be hold responsible for any content that appears on your Website. You agree to protect and defend us against all claims that is rising on your Website. No link(s) should appear on any Website that may be interpreted as libelous, obscene or criminal, or which infringes, otherwise violates, or advocates the infringement or other violation of, any third party rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reservation-of-rights&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reservation of Rights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We reserve the right to request that you remove all links or any particular link to our Website. You approve to immediately remove all links to our Website upon request. We also reserve the right to amen these terms and conditions and it&amp;rsquo;s linking policy at any time. By continuously linking to our Website, you agree to be bound to and follow these linking terms and conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;removal-of-links-from-our-website&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Removal of links from our website&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you find any link on our Website that is offensive for any reason, you are free to contact and inform us any moment. We will consider requests to remove links but we are not obligated to or so or to respond to you directly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we promise to ensure that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up to date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;disclaimer&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions relating to our website and the use of this website. Nothing in this disclaimer will:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;limit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;limit or exclude our or your liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;limit any of our or your liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exclude any of our or your liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The limitations and prohibitions of liability set in this Section and elsewhere in this disclaimer: (a) are subject to the preceding paragraph; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under the disclaimer, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort and for breach of statutory duty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As long as the website and the information and services on the website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABOUT US</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-us---azadi-trust&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Us - Azadi Trust&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Where the Spirit of the Lord is, there is freedom.”&lt;/em&gt; — 2 Corinthians 3:17&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azadi Trust is a small but deeply rooted Christian charity serving &lt;strong&gt;South-East Birmingham&lt;/strong&gt; — a place where diverse cultures meet, and where the need for freedom, peace, and new life is as real as the air we breathe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The name &lt;strong&gt;Azadi&lt;/strong&gt; comes from the Persian word for &lt;em&gt;“freedom” or “liberty”&lt;/em&gt;, a word sung in multiple languages — Luri, Pashto, Kurdish, Hindko, Baluchi, Hindi, Urdu, Punjabi, Bengali, Kashmiri. &lt;em&gt;From its sound alone, you might begin to feel the heartbeat of our mission — to bring freedom to those weighed down, peace to those in turmoil, and new life to all, through the love of Jesus Christ.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-story-following-gods-lead&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Story: Following God’s Lead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It began in &lt;strong&gt;1991&lt;/strong&gt; with Dr. Robin Fisher, a GP in Sparkbrook, moved by compassion for the many drug users in his community.&lt;br&gt;
From a small Christian outreach grew a vision — a vision we still carry today: &lt;em&gt;follow what God is doing&lt;/em&gt; rather than impose our own plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the mid-1990s, when the initial medical and drug work ended, the charity’s heartbeat continued. By &lt;strong&gt;1997&lt;/strong&gt;, with the support of Christ Church, the old GP surgery became &lt;strong&gt;Azadi House&lt;/strong&gt; — our home, our base, and a place of transformation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In those early days, you could hear the &lt;em&gt;laughter of youth clubs&lt;/em&gt;, the &lt;em&gt;soft chatter of homework help sessions&lt;/em&gt;, and the &lt;em&gt;warm welcome of community mothers and toddlers&lt;/em&gt;. Later came football teams like &lt;em&gt;Azadi Tigers&lt;/em&gt;, and projects like &lt;em&gt;Bright Sparks&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;volunteers-and-trustees-the-heart-and-the-hands&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volunteers and Trustees: The Heart and the Hands&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every day, our &lt;strong&gt;volunteers&lt;/strong&gt; bring this mission to life — some offering listening ears, some practical skills, others a strong back or creative spark. Our &lt;strong&gt;trustees&lt;/strong&gt; guide the journey, ensuring every choice honours the founding vision while embracing today’s opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As you picture their dedication, you might begin to notice how your own skills, prayers, or time could weave into this same fabric of care.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;buildings-that-shelter-dreams&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buildings That Shelter Dreams&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Azadi House&lt;/strong&gt; is more than a building. It’s a home for projects like the &lt;strong&gt;Hope Garden&lt;/strong&gt; — where people find healing through soil and friendship, or as a quiet meeting space for grassroots Christian initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We like to see ourselves as a &lt;strong&gt;vehicle&lt;/strong&gt; — one you can step aboard for as long as you need. We provide the structure, governance, insurance, funding support, and network… you just bring your God-given vision, and together, we travel further.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;future-projects-the-road-ahead&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Future Projects: The Road Ahead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In &lt;strong&gt;2010&lt;/strong&gt;, we became a Charitable Company with a new constitution to welcome fresh partnerships — and we’re not stopping here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We envision:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More safe meeting spaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanded community garden projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Greater interfaith bridge-building.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support for more groups who already have the &lt;em&gt;passion&lt;/em&gt; to serve but need the &lt;em&gt;framework&lt;/em&gt; to flourish.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Perhaps right now, you can already imagine the lives waiting to be touched… the doors waiting to open.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-invitation-to-you&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Invitation to You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe freedom is not just something you receive — it’s something you can give.&lt;br&gt;
You can join us through:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Praying for our community.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Volunteering your time or skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharing our story with others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Donating money, food, preloved goods, space, or professional services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Service is the rent we pay for the privilege of living on this earth.”&lt;/em&gt; – Shirley Chisholm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you read this, you may already feel a quiet stirring, sensing that your presence here is no accident — that perhaps, this is your moment to come aboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;experience-our-mission-through-your-senses&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience Our Mission Through Your Senses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feel&lt;/em&gt; the warmth of welcome in Azadi House.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;See&lt;/em&gt; friendship grow where once there were barriers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hear&lt;/em&gt; the laughter of children in safe places.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Know&lt;/em&gt; the peace in helping someone find their freedom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azadi Trust isn’t just about what &lt;em&gt;we&lt;/em&gt; do — it’s about what &lt;strong&gt;we can do together&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Freedom… peace… new life — not just for our neighbours in Birmingham, but also for everyone who chooses to be part of this journey.
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;text-center flex items-center justify-center&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/en/donate&#34;&gt;
&lt;button class=&#34;justify-center items-center rounded-full bg-gradient-to-r from-primary-500 to-primary-600 dark:from-primary-800 dark:to-primary-900 px-8 pt-4 pb-4 sm:px-2 sm:pb-2 text-lg sm:text-base font-semibold text-white shadow-sm hover:bg-primary-500&#34;&gt;
  Donate Now - Transform Lives
&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;meet-our-team&#34;&gt;Meet Our Team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;


&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🕵️ Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This page is published with 
 for 
. Being a 
, it does not collect or share any personal data with third parties. However, it uses external services to add various functionalities, which are detailed in the following list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
 for hosting it&amp;rsquo;s source code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
 for contact form. I will answer your message through your provided email. Please note that GDPR.eu is run by Proton Mail, the world’s largest encrypted email service and recommends end to end encryption for secure communication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
 for serving the page and analytics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
 for the license.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This website and its contents were created in my personal capacity. The views expressed are my own and do not necessarily represent the views of people I have interviewed or taken ideas from their books, videos or/and articles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This website contains links to the websites of third parties („external links“). As the content of these websites is not under my control, I cannot assume any liability for such external content. In all cases, the provider of information of the linked websites is liable for the content and accuracy of the information provided. At the point in time when the links were placed, no infringements of the law were recognizable to me. As soon as an infringement of the law becomes known to me, I will immediately remove the link in question.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🧴 Disclaimer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This website provides general information and discussions about health and related subjects. The information and other content provided on this site, or in any linked materials, are not intended and should not be construed as medical advice, nor is the information a substitute for professional medical expertise or treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you or any other person has a medical concern, you should consult with your health care provider or seek other professional medical treatment. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something that have read on this blog or in any linked materials. If you think you may have a medical emergency, call your doctor or emergency services immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The opinions and views expressed on this site and website have no relation to those of any academic, hospital, health practice or other institution.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
